Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Shop Files, 1951-1998
  - Subseries V:A: General Shop Files, 1951-1998.
    - Herald Tribune: Arbitrations, 1966 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Herald Tribune: Arbitrations, 1967 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Herald Tribune: Arbitrations (Braman, Chester), 1958 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Herald Tribune: Arbitrations (Lockout), 1959 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Herald Tribune: Contracts, 1951-1962 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Herald Tribune: Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Herald Tribune: Correspondence, 1957 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Herald Tribune: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Herald Tribune: General, 1951-1954 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Herald Tribune: General, 1955-1959 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Herald Tribune: General, 1960-1962 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Herald Tribune: General, 1963 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Herald Tribune: General, 1964-1967 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Herald Tribune: Grievances, 1951-1953 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Herald Tribune: Grievances, 1954-1958 (Box 198a, Folder 1)
    - Herald Tribune: Grievances, 1959-1961 (Box 198a, Folder 2)
    - Herald Tribune: Grievances, 1962-1964; 1966 (Box 198a, Folder 3)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations (I), 1952 (Box 198a, Folder 4)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations (II), 1952 (Box 198a, Folder 5)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations (III), 1952 (Box 198a, Folder 6)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations, 1953-1954 (Box 198a, Folder 7)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations, 1956 (Box 198a, Folder 8)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations, 1958 (Box 198a, Folder 9)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations, 1960 (Box 198a, Folder 10)
    - Herald Tribune: Negotiations, 1962-1964 (Box 198a, Folder 11)
    - Herald Tribune: New Lead (Shop Paper), 1951-1961 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Herald Tribune: Organizing, 1955 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Herald Tribune: Organizing, 1961-1962 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Herald Tribune: Payroll, 1963 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Herald Tribune: Pensions, 1952 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Herald Tribune: Pensions, 1957 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Herald Tribune: Pensions, 1958 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel (I), 1951-1952 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel (II), 1951-1952 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel, 1953-1954 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel, 1957 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel, 1958 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel, 1959 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel, 1961 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Herald Tribune: Personnel, 1963-1966 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Herald Tribune: Strike and Merger, 1966 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Herald Tribune: Trial Board (I), 1963 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Herald Tribune: Trial Board (II), 1963 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Herald Tribune: Unit Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Herald Tribune: Welfare, 1964 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Hillman Periodicals: Organizing, 1951 (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Hillman Periodicals: National Labor Relations Board Hearing, 1952 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Home News: Arbitrations, 1979-1981 (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Home News: Contract, 1971-1991 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Home News: General, 1985-1990 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Home News: Grievances, 1980-1981 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Home News: Watch along the Raritan (Shop Paper), 1985-1991 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - International Advisory Council: Contracts, 1971 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - International Advisory Council: Negotiations, 1971-1975 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - International Advisory Council: Grievances, 1971-1975 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - International Literary Centre: Contracts, 1982-1989 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - International Literary Centre: Grievances, 1975-1976; 1981; 1985 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - International Literary Centre: Negotiations, 1976-1982 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - International Literary Centre: Personnel, 1980-1981 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - International News Service and International News Photos: Grievance, 1951-1958 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - International News Service and International News Photos: Negotiations, 1957 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Interstate Broadcasting Company: Arbitrations, 1952 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Interstate Broadcasting Company: Negotiations, 1956-1957 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Jersey Journal: Negotiations, 1961-1963 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Arbitrations, 1962-1969 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Contracts, 1958-1961 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Contracts, 1971-1982 (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Contracts, 1984-1995 (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: General, 1951-1990 (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Grievances, 1952-1959 (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Grievances, 1960-1967 (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Grievances, 1968-1972 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Grievances, 1974-1979 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Grievances, 1980-1987 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Life Insurance, 1978-1979 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Negotiations, 1951-1955 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Negotiations, 1956-1963 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Negotiations, 1970-1974 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Negotiations, 1975 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Negotiations, 1978-1988 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Negotiations, 1993-1995 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Passover Agreement, 1980 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Personnel, 1973-1983 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Jewish Daily Forward: Wages, 1951-1952; 1972-1973 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Arbitrations, 1973; 1988 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Contracts, 1954-1956 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Contracts, 1970-1979 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Contracts, 1983-1995 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: General, 1951-1958 (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: General, 1973-1985 (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Grievances, 1951-1961 (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Grievances, 1962-1971 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Grievances, 1974-1979 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Grievances, 1981-1988 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Jewish Telegraphic Agency (Shop Paper), 1973 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1951-1953 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1960-1963 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1970-1975 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1977-1981 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1981-1992 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Pensions, 1965 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Journal American (New York Journal-American): Arbitrations, 1952 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations, 1956-1957 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations (I), 1958 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations (II), 1958 (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations, 1959-1961 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations, 1962-1965 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations, 1966 (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations (Reinstatement of Messengers) (I), 1954-1956 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Journal American: Arbitrations (Reinstatement of Messengers) (II), 1954-1956 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Journal American: Contracts, 1951-1965 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Journal American: General, 1951-1954 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Journal American: General, 1955-1958 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Journal American: General, 1959-1962 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Journal American: General, 1963 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Journal American: General, 1964 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Journal American: General, 1965-1967 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Journal American: Grievances, 1951-1959 (Box 203a, Folder 1)
    - Journal American: Grievances, 1960-1963 (Box 203a, Folder 2)
    - Journal American: Grievances, 1964-1965; 1979 (Box 203a, Folder 3)
    - Journal American: Leo, Victor (Chairman, Journal American Unit), 1951-1952 (Box 203a, Folder 4)
    - Journal American: Leo, Victor (I), 1953-1955 (Box 203a, Folder 5)
    - Journal American: Leo, Victor (II), 1953-1955 (Box 203a, Folder 6)
    - Journal American: Leo, Victor (III), 1953-1955 (Box 203a, Folder 7)
    - Journal American: Merger, 1959 (Box 203a, Folder 8)
    - Journal American: Negotiations, 1952-1955 (Box 203a, Folder 9)
    - Journal American: Negotiations, 1956-1958 (Box 203a, Folder 10)
    - Journal American: Negotiations (I), 1960-1961 (Box 203a, Folder 11)
    - Journal American: Negotiations (II), 1960-1961 (Box 203a, Folder 12)
    - Journal American: Negotiations, 1962 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Journal American: Negotiations, 1965 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Journal American: Newspaper Guild of New York v. New York Journal American, 1956-1957 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Journal American: Overset (Shop Paper), 1955-1957 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Journal American: Pension, Undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Journal American: Personnel, Undated (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1951-1953 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1954 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1955 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1956 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1957 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1958 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1959 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1961 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Journal American: Personnel, 1963-1966 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Journal American: Personnel (Job Descriptions) (I), 1961 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Journal American: Personnel (Job Descriptions) (II), 1961 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Journal American: Personnel (Requests for Reclassification), 1960-1962 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Journal American: Reopening, 1953-1954 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Journal American: Reslotting, 1954; 1962 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Journal American: Strike Benefits, 1953 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Journal American: Wage Reopening, 1951-1954 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Journal of Commerce: Organizing, Undated; 1975 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Kingston Daily Freeman: Negotiations, 1953; 1960-1964 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Labor Press: Arbitrations, 1959-1961 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Labor Press: Conferences, 1957 (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Labor Press: Contracts, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - Labor Press: General, 1951-1955 (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - Labor Press: General, 1956-1964 (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - Labor Press: General, 1965-1982 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Labor Press: Grievances, 1951-1961 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Labor Press: Grievances, 1962-1975 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Labor Press: Negotiations, 1951-1992 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Labor Press: Negotiations (Hotel and Club Employees Union), 1954-1955 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Labor Press: Negotiations (Hotel Trades Council), 1955 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Labor Press: Negotiations (International Association of Machinists), 1959-1960 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Labor Press: Negotiations (Lithographers and Photoengravers Union), 1966-1967 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Labor Press: Negotiations (National Maritime Union), 1959-1960; 1964 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Labor Press: Negotiations (Transport Workers Union), 1952 (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Labor Press: Roundup (Shop Paper), 1954-1957 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Local 88 Bulletin (International Masters, Mates, and Pilots Union): Negotiations, 1962 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Long Island Daily Press (Long Island Star Journal): Advance Publications Inc. v. Newspaper Guild of New York (Lou O'Neill), 1977-1978 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Advance Publications. v. Newspaper Guild of New York (Lou O'Neill), 1979-1980 (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Bulletin (Shop Paper), 1974 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Contracts, 1951-1978 (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - Long Island Daily Press: General, 1951-1955 (Box 206, Folder 17)
    - Long Island Daily Press: General, 1968-1971 (Box 206, Folder 18)
    - Long Island Daily Press: General, 1972-1975 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1953-1956 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1957-1959 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1960-1963 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1964-1966 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1967-1969 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1970-1973 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1974-1977 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Grievances (Estock, Anne), 1967-1968 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Long Island Daily Press: L. I. Outlook (Shop Paper), 1957 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Long Island Daily Press: National Labor Relations Board, 1958-1966; 1979 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Negotiations, 1957-1959 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Negotiations, 1961-1966 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Negotiations, 1967-1968 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Negotiations, 1971-1974 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Negotiations, 1976-1977 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Organizing, 1954-1968 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Pay Board, 1972-1973 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Pensions, 1963-1978 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Personnel, 1965-1968 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Personnel, 1975; 1977 (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Severance, 1970-1971; 1977 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Strike, 1968-1969 (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Long Island Daily Press: Trial Board, 1967-1969 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Look (Cowles): Contracts, 1951-1956 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Look (Cowles): Contracts, 1956-1965 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Look (Cowles): Contracts, 1965-1967 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Look (Cowles): Contracts, 1967-1972 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Look (Cowles): Forward Look (Shop Paper), 1964; 1970 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Look (Cowles): General, 1951-1964 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Look (Cowles): General, 1965-1971 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Look (Cowles): Grievances, 1952-1964 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Look (Cowles): Grievances, 1965-1968 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Look (Cowles): Grievances, 1969-1971 (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Look (Cowles): Look News (Shop Paper), 1956 (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Look (Cowles): National Labor Relations Board (I), 1967-1968 (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Look (Cowles): National Labor Relations Board (II), 1967-1968 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Look (Cowles): Negotiations, 1952-1958 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Look (Cowles): Negotiations, 1960-1963 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Look (Cowles): Negotiations, 1965 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Look (Cowles): Negotiations (I), 1969 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Look (Cowles): Negotiations (II), 1969 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Look (Cowles): Negotiations (III), 1969 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Look (Cowles): Negotiations, 1971 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Look (Cowles): Organizing, 1951-1958 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Look (Cowles): Organizing, 1967-1969 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Look (Cowles): Personnel, 1964-1971 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Look (Cowles): Reopening, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Look (Cowles): Telephone Directory, 1958 (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - MacFadden Publications: National Labor Relations Board (Election), 1951-1952 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - MacFadden Publications: Negotiations, 1951-1953 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - MacFadden Publications: Organizing, 1951 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Macmillan: Organizing, 1974 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Mademoiselle: Organizing, 1957 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Arbitrations, 1985 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Contracts, 1963; 1973-1975 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Decertification Election, 1985 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Grievances, 1954-1963 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Grievances, 1966-1976 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Grievances, 1977-1980 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Grievances, 1981-1985 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Negotiations, 1954-1961 (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Negotiations, 1963-1974 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Negotiations, 1975-1978 (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Negotiations, 1980-1982 (Box 211, Folder 16)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Negotiations, 1983 (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Personnel, 1970; 1981-1983 (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Straight Talk (Shop Paper), 1957 (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - Magazine Antiques (Straight Enterprises): Welfare, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Arbitrations, 1976-1978 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Contract, 1976 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: General, 1975-1978 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Grievances, 1976-1978 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Magazine Management (Shop Paper), 1975-1976 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: National Labor Relations Board, 1978 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Negotiations (I), 1975-1976 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Negotiations (II), 1975-1976 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Organizing, 1972-1975 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Magazine Management Company, Inc.: Personnel, 1977-1978 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Magazine Field: Organizing, 1967 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - McGraw Hill: Organizing, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Medical Journals: Negotiations, 1972 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Medical Journals: Negotiations, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Medical World News: Organizing, 1966 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Metro: Organizing, 1973 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Microfilming Corporation of America: Organizing, 1973 (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Morning Freiheit: General, 1951-1971 (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Morning Journal (Jewish Journal and Daily News): Contracts, 1951-1953 (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Morning Journal: General, 1951-1953 (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - Morning Journal: Grievances, 1951-1953 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Morning Journal: Negotiations, 1951-1952 (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - Morning Journal: Suspension, 1953 (Box 212, Folder 23)
    - Morning Telegraph: Arbitrations, 1951-1966 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Morning Telegraph: Arbitrations, 1968-1973 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Morning Telegraph: Contracts, 1951-1964 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Morning Telegraph: Contracts, 1966-1971 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Morning Telegraph: General, 1951-1964 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Morning Telegraph: General, 1965-1972 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Morning Telegraph: Grievances, 1951-1962 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Morning Telegraph: Grievances, 1963-1972 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Morning Telegraph: Job Descriptions, 1964 (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Morning Telegraph: National Labor Relations Board, 1972-1973 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1951-1960 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1962-1965 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1967-1969 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1970 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Morning Telegraph: Organizing, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Morning Telegraph: Personnel, 1963-1965 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Morning Telegraph: Personnel, 1966-1969 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Morning Telegraph: Personnel, 1970 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Morning Telegraph: Personnel, 1971-1972 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Morning Telegraph: Referendum, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Morning Telegraph: Reopening, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Morning Telegraph: Strike, 1972 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Morning Telegraph: Suspension, 1972 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Morning Telegraph: Welfare, 1972-1973 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Municipal Photographers: Arbitrations, 1971 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Municipal Photographers: Certification, 1959-1960 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Municipal Photographers: Contracts, 1958-1973 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Municipal Photographers: Dues, 1961-1963 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Municipal Photographers: Dues, 1969-1970 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Municipal Photographers: Fact Finding Hearing (I), 1970 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Municipal Photographers: Fact Finding Hearing (II) (copies of photos including Sanitation Department's antilitter campaign with Journal American "calendar girls" and Park Slope plane crash), 1960; 1970 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Municipal Photographers: Fact Finding Report, 1970 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Municipal Photographers: Fact Finding Report (dissent), 1970 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Municipal Photographers: General, 1955-1970 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Municipal Photographers: General, 1971-1973 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Municipal Photographers: General, 1974-1975 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Municipal Photographers: Grievances, 1962-1964 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Municipal Photographers: Grievances, 1965 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Municipal Photographers: Grievances, 1966-1968 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Municipal Photographers: Grievances, 1971-1974 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Municipal Photographers: Job Descriptions, 1963-1964 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Municipal Photographers: Job Descriptions, 1970 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1957-1959 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1962-1963 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1964-1965 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1966-1968 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1969-1971 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1972 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1973 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Municipal Photographers: Negotiations, 1974 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Municipal Photographers: Police Photographers, 1968-1970 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Municipal Photographers: Teamsters Petition, 1974 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Municipal Photographers: Unit Elections, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 8)